gamelytic.com 2019-05-03

# Privacy and Terms of Use

_Gamelytic.com and our network of websites_  are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and using information responsibly. Please read below for detailed information about our privacy policy.

 **How we use information**

Our site does not store personal information we collect in order to process transactions for commercial purposes. Contact information (email address, telephone number, address, etc.) from the order form is used to send your orders and information about our company to you. Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary.

Financial information (credit card numbers, credit card expiration dates, billing address, etc.) that is collected is used only to bill you for products and services and not stored. Information collected on any of our forms may only be used to contact you, whether in person or via automated emails in response to your form submission.Your financial and payment information is processed solely through Paypal and we do not hold or process any of the financial information.

 **Cookies**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser. They make it possible for us to store contents of your shopping box until you are ready to check out and recognize your browser when you visit. By doing this, we can personalize your return visits and save you time during checkout. In order to enjoy the benefits of being a registered user, your browser must be set to accept cookies.

We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners.

 **How we collect information**

This site uses a secure server (SSL) certified by Thawte to encrypt all of your personal information. We use strong security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of your information once it is in our records.

 **Your agreement**

By using our web site or purchasing a product from us, you agree to the collection and use of information as set forth in this privacy policy. We may from time to time update this policy. We will post any changes to our policy on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

 **Commitment to customer service**

 _Gamelytic.com_ is committed to quality customer experience. We are constantly reviewing your feedback to improve and enhance your shopping experience. You can tell us what you think by contacting our customer care department through email at _sale@Gamelytic.com_.

 **Authorized third parties**

We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, an industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information about the user is collected or used in this process. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, go to: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

 **We also use third party advertisements on Gamelytic.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in yourbrowser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.**

We also work with a third party to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic and other advertising statistics. Where authorized by us, this third party may use cookies and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is transferred to this third party.

 **Terms of Use**  
YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK AND THAT THE SERVICES ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE.” GAMELYTIC GAMING, ITS SUBSIDIARIES AND AFFILIATES, AND ITS LICENSORS DO NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT TO YOU THAT: (A) YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, (B) YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE OR FREE FROM ERROR, (C) ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED BY YOU AS A RESULT OF YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE, AND (D) THAT DEFECTS IN THE OPERATION OR FUNCTIONALITY OF ANY SOFTWARE PROVIDED TO YOU AS PART OF THE SERVICES WILL BE CORRECTED. ANY MATERIAL DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE SERVICES IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR OTHER DEVICE OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIAL.

In short, we try our best to make sure our game guides are up to date. But we cannot guarantee that they will be up to date all the time.
